ntent.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy - NTENT

### Introduction

Thank you for visiting NTENT. Your privacy is very important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this document explaining our online information practices and the choices you have regarding our collection and use of data. This document is intended to provide complete transparency about the activities we engage in, the types of data we collect, how we use such data, how we retain and secure such data, and your right to opt out of certain types of data collection and use.

### Information We Collect

When you visit a page that contains advertisements provided by us, we may collect certain information about your computer or device. This information may include your Internet browser, your IP address, the sites you visit, your operating system and version, and other information. When you interact with our products and services, we may collect additional information about your interactions such as your search queries, products you view, and click-through data.

We collect information by using web beacons and setting cookies on your computer or mobile device. A cookie is a small text file that is created on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Our cookies contain a unique string that we use to anonymously identify your browser or mobile device while keeping your identify hidden. A web beacon is programming code used to display a pixel on a website, which allows a third party who serves the pixel to set a cookie or collect certain data.

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) that uniquely or individually identifies you, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, financial account number, government-issued identifier, or any other information used or intended to be used to identify, contact, or precisely locate you. We do not collect any sensitive non-PII relating to your medical history, race or ethnicity, religious or political affiliations, or sexuality.

We may combine the information we collect from you with online or offline information provided by one or more third parties in order to provide you with better, more relevant advertising. For example, we may provide you with advertisements for local products or events by matching your IP address with publicly available IP / location references, or we may display advertisements for products you have demonstrated an interest in on one or more of our affiliates’ websites.

### Information we share with third parties

We may share information we have collected from you with (1) law enforcement agencies pursuant to a valid court order; (2) selected advertising clients utilizing our conversion tracking services; (3) business partners for the purpose of combating fraudulent activity; and (4) publishers, affiliates and other trusted business partners to improve the quality of advertising you see on our network.

Publishers and other third parties may set cookies of their own. These cookies are beyond the scope of our control and not covered under this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of every site you interact with, especially before providing any personal information.

### Data Retention and Security

We retain the data we collect only as long as necessary to continue to provide you with the most accurate, relevant advertising possible, or as required by law. We may maintain data indefinitely for auditing purposes or to report on and improve our own business practices. We take data security very seriously and undertake all commercially reasonable safeguarding procedures, at least commensurate with industry best practices.

### Changes to This Policy

Our privacy policy may change periodically. We will post conspicuous notice of any material change on our website, www.ntent.com, and we encourage you to review this document from time to time to keep yourself familiar with our practices.
